Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/trần-đình-phúc-b64a4478 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

JavaScript HTML

Java

Trần Đình Phúc

Backend Developer

Phường Đại Kim

Summary

Backend Developer - Technologies used: PHP, Java Core, Java Spring, Java Spring Boot, Oracle, ReactJs, Kafka, Elasticsearch. Also have experience working with linux, docker, kubernetes, gitlab, caching, logging, monitoring, tracing.

Love motocycle, animal, photography, football, and travel.

Experience

PVcomBank Software Developer December 2019 - Present (2 years) Hoàn Kiếm District, Hanoi, Vietnam

Skylink

Software Developer October 2014 - September 2019 (5 years)

Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

Peacesoft Software Developer June 2014 - October 2014 (5 months) Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

Education

Aprotrain Aptech (2012 - 2014)

Activity

11/01/2021, Viewed by Nga Lê (Lenka)